pyramidcollection.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy - Pyramid Collection Customer Service

## PRIVACY POLICY

### Effective Date of Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 4/22/2013. 

Welcome to the Pyramid Collection website. We know you care how your personal information is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust in us. 

By "personal information" we mean information that identifies you (such as your name, home address, billing address, telephone number, and email address). “Personal information” also includes descriptive information (such as your style preferences) if coupled with identifying information. 

What personal information do we collect at our website? 

There are two basic types of personal information collected at our website. There is the information you provide directly through the website and the information collected through technology. 

  1. Information Directly Provided by You

We may collect personal information directly from you such as your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone number, email address, credit card number, order information, and sizing information. This information may be collected in various places, such as when you visit our website and take any of the following actions: 

    * Place an order, fill out a form, subscribe to a catalog, or request information about our products and services;
    * Participate in interactive features of the website or mobile applications, such as product reviews;
    * Use a social media service such as our Facebook page or YouTube channel;
    * Create a gift registry or shopping list;
    * Sign up for e-mails, mobile messages, or social media notifications from us; or
    * Enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to one of our surveys, or participate in a focus group.

We may also collect information that you provide about people you know, such as a recipient's contact information when you send a gift or order gift cards. 

  2. Information Collected through Technology

During a normal visit to our website, we may collect information such as the amount of time spent on our site, the pages you visit, clicks, page views, browser type and version, service-provider identification, and IP address. Such information is collected in the aggregate and is anonymous in that it does not contain information that directly identifies you. However, such information may become non-anonymous to the extent that it becomes coupled with personal information provided by you. 

As you interact with our service, we and our service providers may place cookies on your system. Cookies are small files that are sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer for record keeping purposes. In general, cookies make the Internet more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular system. They help us to improve our website, personalize your shopping experience, and provide you with better customer service. 

In addition to cookies, we and our service providers use a variety of other technologies such as web beacons or GIF tags to personalize your experience and gather information on how users interact with our website. This technology allows us to associate your online interactions, such as the pages you visit on our website, your purchase information, and IP-based geographic location, with the personal information you provided to us. The technology also allows us to provide features such as saving items in your cart between visits and delivering product recommendations that are relevant to your prior purchase(s) or browsing history. We also use this information for reporting and analysis purposes in order to improve our business, to market products and services on our website and other websites and over various media, and to deliver products and services to you. 

We use third-party companies to serve ads on other websites. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites collected through cookies and GIF tags in order to provide personalized banner and display advertisements for goods and services when you visit other websites, based on your interactions and purchases. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice and to know your choices with respect to these third party services, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ or www.aboutads.info. 

Most browsers include in the toolbar help section instructions on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable cookies. 

How do we use the information collected at our website? 

Personal information we collect at our website may be used to do things like the following: 

  * To process your orders and information requests;
  * To improve customer service, whether its following up on an order or responding to a technical support request;
  * To personalize your online experience with offers and content tailored to your individual preferences and needs;
  * To improve our website, as we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you;
  * To administer contests, promotions, surveys and other website features;
  * To enable you to post your feedback and other content;
  * To enable you to interact with third-party content and service providers, whether by viewing their content on our website or within their own environment, or by linking directly to their websites; and
  * To market products and services for our various brands (such as adding to our or any of our sister brand’s email list or print catalog list when you make an online purchase).

How does our website interact with third party websites and content providers? 

Our website may provide links to third party sites or display content provided by third parties. These sites and content providers’ own privacy policies and terms of site use will govern your experience on these sites or interaction with this content, and we encourage you to review these policies and terms of site use. Links or third party content provided on our website may include the following: 

  1. Security Certifications

We may provide links to the websites of certain companies or organizations that provide security certifications of our website. The third party’s privacy policy applies to any personal information you may provide at its website. 

  2. Sweepstakes, Contests, Surveys, and other Promotions

We may provide sweepstakes, contests, surveys, or other promotions on our website for which we use the services of a third party provider. To the extent that the third party provider is running the promotion, any personal information you may provide in connection with the promotion may be governed by the privacy policy of the third party provider. In such a case, please review the third party provider’s privacy policy. 

  3. Maps

We may provide access to online mapping functionality delivered by content providers such as Yahoo!, Google, and Microsoft. The third party content provider’s privacy policy applies to any personal information you may provide at its website. 

  4. Social Networking and other User-Generated Content Sites

We may include links to social networking sites and other sites that host user-generated content. The third-party's privacy policy applies to any personal information you may provide at its website. 

  5. Membership Programs or Reward Sites

We may enter into relationships with certain third party companies that offer membership in programs providing discounts, rewards, and/or other benefits for certain purchases (which may include purchases from our website). If you become a member of any of these programs or make a purchase on our website through any of these programs, we may provide the company administering any such program information about you or your purchase (such as your name and the transaction details) to enable it to honor your terms of membership. These companies’ maintain their own privacy policies and terms of use which will govern your experience with them, and we encourage you to review these policies and terms of use. 

What information is shared with or accessed by third parties and our own sister brands? 

  1. Our Sister Brands

We may share certain information described in this Privacy Policy (such as your mailing address, email address, order history, and indicated preferences) with our sister brands within Potpourri Group, Inc. so they may market their own products. Click here to view a current list of our sister brands. 

  2. Service Providers

We use third parties to provide certain support services to us. These third party service providers do things like fulfill orders, provide customer service, process orders and payments, provide call center services, administer sweepstakes and other promotions, manage premiums and coupons, maintain databases, provide web hosting, print and distribute catalogs and marketing materials, administer and monitor emails, provide analytics, send mobile messaging, provide marketing services, and display advertisements on our website and other websites. For these and other functions, such third party service providers may receive or have access to your personal information. 

  3. Other Companies for Marketing

We may share your name, postal address and purchase information with other merchants who may use this information to send you offers for the merchant’s own products and services. To opt-out of our sharing your information with such other merchants, please email info@PyramidCollection.com or call 1-877-756-1628. 

  4. Compliance with Law

We may provide access to specific information about our website visitors when legally required to do so, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website, to limit our legal liability, and to protect our rights or to protect the rights, property, or safety of our customers, the public, or our business. 

  5. Merger, Sale or other Transaction

In the event of any reorganization, restructuring, merger or sale, or other transfer of our business assets, including a brand or line of business, consumer information may be one of the business assets that are transferred in connection with such transaction. We may transfer personal information in the event of such a transaction. This Privacy Policy does not restrict our ability to share aggregated or anonymized information that does not directly identify any individual. 

What Choices do you have regarding the use of your Personal Information? 

  1. Email

Your email address may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to an order, in addition to company news, updates, related product or service information, and special offers and promotions, including from any of our sister brands. You may stop future delivery of these emails by following the opt-out or “unsubscribe” instructions located at the bottom of each such email. Please note that opting out or unsubscribing to any of these emails will not stop your receipt of transactional emails (such as email confirmations of your online orders or customer service communications from the brand from which you placed your order). In the event we provide you with the opportunity to opt in to receive email messages from third parties, if you do choose to opt in, we will share your e-mail information with the specific third party. In such an event, please review the privacy policy of the third party for how it treats your personal information. 

  2. Catalogs

If you choose not to receive a print catalog or other mailed marketing materials from us or any of our sister brands, please email info@PyramidCollection.com or call 1-877-756-1628. 

  3. Cookies, Gif Tags, and Banner or Display Advertising

Cookies placed by us (first party) or third party service providers on our website provide us with important information on how visitors use our website, and enable us to deliver our ads on our website as well as other websites. You can block or clear cookies from your computer by following your browser’s instructions. To block online advertising which may appear on other websites based on your online activity on our site, you can click the preference icon that appears on most banner or display advertising. To learn more about your choices with respect to third party advertising, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ or www.aboutads.info. 

How do we protect your information? 

We take information security very seriously and use reasonable administrative, technical, physical and managerial measures to protect your personal information from unauthorized access. For example, we utilize Secure Sockets Layering (an industry-standard data tranmission protocol) in order to encrypt certain data transmissions that contains personal information you send to us through ordering, or registration, or sign up processes. 

No system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of your information and cannot assume liability for improper access. 

How do you make changes to your personal information? 

You may update or modify your account information by calling 1-877-756-1628. 

Children’s Privacy 

Protecting children's privacy is important to us. We do not collect or retain any information from anyone we actually know is under the age of 13, and no part of our website is targeted to anyone under 13. We also do not send email correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13 without their parent's consent. 

Children under the age of 13 should always ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any personal information to anyone online. We urge parents and guardians to participate in their children's online activities and use parental control or other web filtering technology to supervise children's access to the Web. 

Your California Privacy Rights 

We collect various types of personal information about you during the course of our customer relationship. Under California law, California residents may make a written request to us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we may have shared with third parties or our corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. Upon receiving your written request, we may provide you with a notice describing how to opt-out of our sharing your information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. 

If you are a California resident and would like to exercise your rights under California law, please send your written request or email to: 

Potpourri Group, Inc.  
101 Billerica Ave, Building 2  
North Billerica, MA 01862  
Attention: Customer Service  
E-mail: info@PyramidCollection.com  

Please include your mailing address so that we may provide you with our notice and third party direct marketing opt-out form. Please allow thirty (30) days to receive a response. Please note that this opt-out does not prohibit disclosures made for non-marketing purposes. 

Please review our Privacy Policy if you would like to know more about what information is gathered about you at our website and how it is used. 

Changes to our Privacy Policy 

Occasionally we may update this Privacy Policy in order to reflect any changes to the website or our privacy practices. If we make any material updates to this statement, the new statement will be posted to the website ten (10) days prior to the changes taking effect. 

Questions about our Privacy Policy 

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at: 

Potpourri Group, Inc.  
101 Billerica Ave, Building 2  
North Billerica, MA 01862  
Attention: Customer Service  
E-mail: info@PyramidCollection.com  
Telephone: 1-877-756-1628
